- I've spent
the past seven years
traveling the world,
perfecting my craft.
You see, I'm something
of a magician,
inventor and chocolate maker.
So quiet up and listen down.
Nope. Scratch that, reverse it.
- Mr. Wonka, I can see you're
a man of great ingenuity.
- What are you doing?
- I'm making chocolate,
of course.
How do you like it?
Dark? White? Nutty?
Absolutely insane?
- Many people have come here
to sell chocolate.
They've all been crushed...
by The Chocolate Cartel.
You can't get a shop
without selling chocolate,
and you can't sell chocolate
without a shop.
-No daydreaming.
-What are we gonna do, Willy?
-Huh.
-Huh?
-A double-huh.
-Do you have a pencil and paper?
-Uh-huh.
-I got an idea.
I know things haven't
been easy for you.
They're gonna get better.
-You promise?
-I pinkie promise.
That's the most solemn vow
there is.
-Where do we start?
-A good chocolate
should be simple.
-Whereas this, it's just...
-Weird.
-CROWD: Whoa!
-What's happening?
Who wants a chocolate
that makes you fly?
- Well, let's find out,
shall we?
Who's for Hoverchoc?
-[giggles]
-Nothin' to see here.
Just a small group of people
defyin' the laws of gravity.
-Ladies and gentlemen
of The Galeries Gourmet,
my name is Willy Wonka.
-He's good..
-Too good.
-[grunts]
-Pretty sure I've gained
about 150 pounds
in the last two weeks.
-You could change
her life, Mr. Wonka,
change all their lives.
-Run away!
-Every good thing in this world
started with a dream.
So you hold on to yours.
-[whispers]
Here we go, Mama.
Mark my words,
this is gonna be
the greatest chocolate shop...
...the world has ever seen.
So you're the funny little man
who's been following me.
-I will have you know
that I am a perfectly
respectable size...
for an Oompa Loompa.
-An Oompa-what-now?
-Allow me to refresh
your memory.
[ethereal music]
-Oh, I don't think
I wanna hear that.
-Too late.
I've started dancing now.
Once we've started,
we can't stop.